// letters used for levels 1-3
const letters = {
  upperLetters: 'ABCDEFGHIJKLMNOPQRSTUVWXYZ',
  lowerLetters: 'abcdefghijklmnopqrstuvwxyz',
  mixLetters: 'ABCDEFGHIJKLMNOPQRSTUVWXYZabcdefghijklmnopqrstuvwxyz',
};

// special characters used for level 7
const specialChars = ',.!@#$%^&*()"<>[]-=+_?\';:';

// short animal words used in level 4
const shortAnimals = [
  { problem: 'ğŸ„', answer: 'cow' },
  { problem: 'ğŸˆ', answer: 'cat' },
  { problem: 'ğŸ•', answer: 'dog' },
  { problem: 'ğŸ…', answer: 'tiger' },
  { problem: 'ğŸ', answer: 'horse' },
  { problem: 'ğŸ–', answer: 'pig' },
  { problem: 'ğŸ', answer: 'mouse' },
  { problem: 'ğŸ¦†', answer: 'duck' },
  { problem: 'ğŸ¦‰', answer: 'owl' },
  { problem: 'ğŸ¸', answer: 'frog' },
  { problem: 'ğŸ', answer: 'snake' },
  { problem: 'ğŸ¦ˆ', answer: 'shark' },
  { problem: 'ğŸŒ', answer: 'snail' },
  { problem: 'ğŸ•·ï¸', answer: 'spider' },
  { problem: 'ğŸ', answer: 'bee' },
  { problem: 'ğŸ¦¥', answer: 'sloth' },
  { problem: 'ğŸ¦¨', answer: 'skunk' },
  { problem: 'ğŸ»', answer: 'bear' },
  { problem: 'ğŸ¦', answer: 'lion' },
  { problem: 'ğŸ¦Š', answer: 'fox' },
  { problem: 'ğŸº', answer: 'wolf' },
  { problem: 'ğŸ°', answer: 'rabbit' },
  { problem: 'ğŸ ', answer: 'fish' },
  { problem: 'ğŸ³', answer: 'whale' },
  { problem: 'ğŸ¦ˆ', answer: 'shark' },
  { problem: 'ğŸ¢', answer: 'turtle' },
  { problem: 'ğŸ‘', answer: 'sheep' },
  { problem: 'ğŸ', answer: 'goat' },
  { problem: 'ğŸ¦Œ', answer: 'deer' },
  { problem: 'ğŸ¦…', answer: 'eagle' },
  { problem: 'ğŸœ', answer: 'ant' },
  { problem: 'ğŸ¦‡', answer: 'bat' },
];

const bodyParts = [
  { problem: 'ğŸ–ï¸', answer: 'hand' },
  { problem: 'ğŸ‘Š', answer: 'fist' },
  { problem: 'ğŸ¦µ', answer: 'leg' },
  { problem: 'ğŸ¦¶', answer: 'foot' },
  { problem: 'ğŸ’ª', answer: 'arm' },
  { problem: 'ğŸ‘‚', answer: 'ear' },
  { problem: 'ğŸ‘ƒ', answer: 'nose' },
  { problem: 'ğŸ§ ', answer: 'brain' },
  { problem: 'ğŸ‘€', answer: 'eyes' },
  { problem: 'ğŸ‘ï¸', answer: 'eye' },
  { problem: 'ğŸ¦·', answer: 'tooth' },
  { problem: 'ğŸ¦´', answer: 'bone' },
  { problem: 'ğŸ‘„', answer: 'mouth' },
  { problem: 'ğŸ‘…', answer: 'tongue' },
  { problem: 'ğŸ‘£', answer: 'feet' },
  { problem: 'ğŸ©¸', answer: 'blood' },
  { problem: 'ğŸ¤²', answer: 'hands' },
  { problem: 'ğŸ‘¶', answer: 'baby' },
  { problem: 'ğŸ§â€â™‚ï¸', answer: 'man' },
  { problem: 'ğŸ§â€â™€ï¸', answer: 'woman' },
  { problem: 'ğŸ‘', answer: 'thumb' },
];

const colors = [
  { problem: 'ğŸŸ¥', answer: 'red' },
  { problem: 'ğŸ”´', answer: 'red' },
  { problem: 'ğŸ”º', answer: 'red' },
  { problem: 'â¬œ', answer: 'white' },
  { problem: 'âšª', answer: 'white' },
  { problem: 'â¬›', answer: 'black' },
  { problem: 'âš«', answer: 'black' },
  { problem: 'ğŸŸ¦', answer: 'blue' },
  { problem: 'ğŸ”µ', answer: 'blue' },
  { problem: 'ğŸ”·', answer: 'blue' },
  { problem: 'ğŸŸ«', answer: 'brown' },
  { problem: 'ğŸŸ¤', answer: 'brown' },
  { problem: 'ğŸŸ©', answer: 'green' },
  { problem: 'ğŸŸ¢', answer: 'green' },
  { problem: 'ğŸŸ¨', answer: 'yellow' },
  { problem: 'ğŸŸ¡', answer: 'yellow' },
  { problem: 'ğŸŸª', answer: 'purple' },
  { problem: 'ğŸŸ£', answer: 'purple' },
  { problem: 'ğŸŸ§', answer: 'orange' },
  { problem: 'ğŸŸ ', answer: 'orange' },
  { problem: 'ğŸ”¶', answer: 'orange' },
];

export { letters, specialChars, shortAnimals, bodyParts, colors };
